oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
You're making a fist bump.
You're not clingy!
It's your sister.
Stop it! Put that weird bedding on!
Wait, I'm scared
Wait, I'm scared.
Hello!
Welcome, everyone!
What does that mean?
Oh!
Today is my first time!
We are in Iwate!
Oh!
Thank you very much!
Nice to meet you!
It's been a long time!
This is my first time to come to Iwate with IGIYARI GUNLAN!
It's my first time, and I haven't seen you at a show recently.
It's been a while, but this is the first time this year, right?
First time!
I'm so happy!
Yay!
Yay! That's a first!
I'm sorry, but today is my home.
I'm taking the liberty of presiding over this event.
Please do me a favor!
Follow me!
Have fun!
Yes, I know, I know...
What a surprise! In January of this year, my hometown
Morioka City in Iwate was featured in the New York Times
in the 52 Places to Go in 2023.
second only to London to be honored.
Yay!
Second place to London!
It was London?
That's amazing! Second in the world.
That's great!
You must be so proud.
Yes, I am.
That's why today I'm going to tell you one of the reasons why we were chosen.
Iwate Prefecture's specialty, wanko soba!
We are going to experience it at Azumaya Honten!
Yay!
Please do!
Have you ever tried wanko soba?
No!
New first time!
Have you?
Yes, I have!
Is this the place?
Yeah!
Today, we were divided into three teams.
Each team will have 15 minutes to complete their goal.
We are aiming for a total of 571 cups for the 3 teams!
Why?
571 cups.
Why 571 drinks?
The record for the most drinks by a woman in the restaurant is 570.
What?
How did you do that?
571.
What?
One?
Just one?
What?
That's amazing!
Nine people.
Nine people trying to update it.
Nine people, 571 drinks.
One.
That's right.
I wish I could do it.
I wish I could surpass that record of 9 people!
I'll do my best!
We'll definitely surpass it!
We can do it!
We can do it!We can go above and beyond!
Thumbnail.
No, no, no, no, no
Thumbnail is a wanker
This is crazy.
Okay, everyone, let's get to it.
You're all enthusiastic, aren't you?
Yes!
I'll do my best!
That's enough.
Let's go inside the store.
I'm going to give it a try!
Let's go!
Next notice
We are in the store!
We're interrupting you!
Let's go to Team Hapiyo.
Yes, we are.
Okay, first team.
Hai.
What are the names of the three teams?
What is your team name?
Team,
Hapiyon.
Because it is a doggy shova,
Doggie.
I see.
Four years.
I didn't think of it now,
From the beginning.
That's right.
From now.
OK, OK, OK.
Absolutely right.
Then the second team.
Yes.
We are the se.
Curly curly.
They're all cute.
Cute.
The goal is,
Even if you eat a big meal,
Even if you eat too much or too fast,
I will not forget that I am an idol,
I'll be Curikururu.
Wow.
I see.
Yo. Yo.
Wow.
You have to be idle.
Yes, I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
And the last team.
Yes.
Our team name is,
Se-no.
The cutest in the world,
The grand prix for the world's cutest butterfall eater,
Garisto, who doesn't eat,
Long.
Eat up.
Eat it.
We're a team of awesome.
Are you saying we are a great team?
I'd like to ask for the Grand Prix.
I'm sure there will be others.
I love it so much.
I'm sure you'll like it,
So, the three teams are like this.
Yes.
We're not going to fight,
No, we are not fighting.
Nine people,
Yes, yes.
We are aiming for a total of 571 cups,We are aiming for a total of 571 cups, so,
We will do our best in the team competition.
We will do our best.
So, we are prepared.
Yay.
It's gorgeous, isn't it?
Come on, after all, there's pasta now,
This is probably full, right?
This is amazing.
This is enough for 60 bowls.
Wow.
I'm so happy.
We're the first team,
Please do your best to give us momentum.
I'll do my best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Well, let's get started, shall we?
Here we go.
Ready.
Start.
Oh.
Wow.
That's great.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Amazing.
Hang in there, papillon.
That's great.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Here you go.
He's cute.
Amazing.
She's cute.
Good luck!
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
When they say go for it,
Should I ask her name?
What is it?
Yes, I'll do my best.
Yes, I will.
Uichan's pace is great.
Yes, he is.
Oh, wow.
I'll be careful.
Okay, okay.
That makes five cups.
Oh.
That's great.
It's surprisingly good.
Really?
Here you go.
Is it good?
Spicy!
Failed.
Soba?
Soba, soba.
Go for soba.
It's okay.
Looks good.
Kitsiste Shinju.
Manaikmalion.
Yes.
Kitziste Divine Beast.
Long time no see.
Looks delicious.
Delicious.
I'm looking forward to having some condiments.
It tastes amazing.That tastes amazing.
Everyone thinks so.
I don't know.
It's delicious.
Uichan's looks good too.
Last.
Okay, I'm going.
I'll be done in about 15 minutes, and I'll be back at 5:30.
You're amazing, Rui.
That's great.
Aim for 60 cups.
Mr. Mori, wow, that's a lot of food for one person.
That's amazing.
Really? That's amazing.
That's great. I can do it. You can do it.
Go for it.
This is how I'm going to do it.
Let's do it this way.
Cheers.
The condiments are good. After all.
Yes, it is. It's nice.
Cheers.
I don't know, if we do that,
I think there should be a Marliesse.
Oh, I had a hard time here.
Spicy?
Spicy.
Spicy! Spicy! Spicy!
Water buns?
Spicy. Spicy. Spicy.
This makes 30 cups.
Amazing!
That's great!
Hang in there.
Are you okay? It's spicy.
Here you go. 30 cups.
That's enough for two luchers.
That's great!
You haven't even taken half yet, and you're halfway through.
That's right.
It's only a third, but it's great.
Here you go, Tamin.
Is it seaweed?
I put too much in.
It's already 300 cups.
The third cup.
Is it seaweed?
What is the most refreshing condiment?
Pickles.
Oh, really?
Really?
It's the best!
Okay.
What's your favorite condiment, Kaya?
Hmm?
Yes, bread bread.
Pangbang!
They're all pickles.
Then I want it on my bread.
Bon appétit!
It's getting a little tight.
Whatever you feel like.
But we're all pretty hungry.
Yeah, I said we were hungry for some reason.
Thanks to you, we're watching the video.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a lot more fun than I thought it would be.
Fifty minutes to go.
I'll do my best.
I'm fine.
Good luck.
Are you eating here?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
That's great.
Families.
They help me with this tower.
That thing is so deep in the face...If you're too deep in the face with that or
Johnny's if you don't close the bottom.
That's so cool.
It's cool.
Put it on, please.
I'll wait around.
If they're all good, then they're all good, right?
I think I can do it.
I was aiming for 900.
I aimed for it.
I aimed for 100.
I can't do it.
I'm going to eat very slowly.
Mr. Kanya!
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I've had 65 cups.
Let me know how you like it.
One more to go and I'll have 60.
I feel like I've had about 45 cups.
I'm not sure if I need the condiments or not.
I see.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
That's 60 cups.
That's great!
It's done.
You know, I stole the lid, and then I ran away.
One second.
Sixty-four cups.
That's great.
I'm not done yet.
I can do 70.
You got three minutes.
That's good.
Seven minutes.
Oh, my God.
I'm so excited.
You guys take it easy.
You're so cool.
That's your sister.
She's so cool!
She's cute!
That's what I'm talking about!
Hey! - Hey!
Hey, sis!
Cute
Cute!
Hey, sis.
That's 640 cups.
70.
Oh, my God.
Seventy.
I'm over my past self.
That's great.
Shinji, the lid's closed.
It's closed.
You don't have the lid?
Here's the lid.
I'll see you later.
Please sit down.
Which one goes first?
Welcome!
Ma'am.
Please go
Please go!
Come on!
Go, go, go!
I'm not going to say it again
Absolutely, absolutely...
Your sister's in Germany, isn't she?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Are you stopping for a minute, Akan?
Are you okay? Hang in there.
I did my best!
Flap, flap, flap, flap, flap.
I'm new here.
You're not new.
Go for it, rookie!
Yes, I'm new!
Sixty-seven.67
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great!
19, 20, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, done!
That's great!
Thank you for your hard work, sister!
Thank you very much!
So, Papian team is done!
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm so tired!
Yes, I ate 65 bowls of wanko soba!
Yes, I ate 71 bowls!
Yes, Bun-chan had 78 bowls!
Total, a whopping 214 bowls!
Wow! It's Valentine's Day!
At this rate, I'm afraid I can't afford it!
How much are we at? 386 to go?
That's amazing!
Let's move on to the next team!
So, that's it, the Curculion is ready!
Let's go for it!
The first team was amazing.
We're going to try to achieve our quota, too,
I would like to achieve my quota and aim for 60 for now.
I'm looking forward to working even harder.
I'm looking forward to working with the officials!
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Bon appétit!
Go for it!
Delicious!
Yummy!
Ai!
Here you go!
Bon appétit!
You, too, Ai!
And we'll have some, too.
Bon appétit!
With Ai.
I want you to be sweet!
Ai and Ai.
Delicious!
It was a little bad.
It's good, Ai!
Delicious!
You too, Ai.
And Ai.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
I'm afraid to make eye contact.
Good luck!
Yummy!
Ooh!
Thank you for watching!
Did you find the kitchen?
Here you go.
Your sister is the best.
Sister?
Too much sister.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's too loud and too expensive when they find out.
A-chan!
Yuuka-chan!
Don't do it!
Yuka-chan
It's been almost 5 minutes now.
That's so great!
That's a great pace!
I think I can do it!
If it's the 100th one, I'll
I'll make it my title.
I'll put it in my profile.
What should I write in my profile?
Write in my profile
Campaign
What lines do you want me to say?
I'm the only one in the middle.
If you're in the middle, I want you to say something.
Lines you want me to say?What do you want me to say?
Go ahead, Yu-chan.
It was a kill roomie.
I'm in a different frame of mind.
Sixty glasses.
Good luck, Karen.
Do me a favor.
Yay!
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's funny.
Ramen
It's done!
This one is finished too!
So cool!
How many cups is this?
Two cups.
If you eat 2 cups, you get 60.
That's amazing.
This is amazing.
Oh, my God.
I'm not specifying what a person becomes.
What are you going to do?
I'm in.
Let's make it a big number.
A thousand?
A thousand.
Good luck.
How many 100s?
A thousand.
One thousand.
15 cups.
Looks tough.
Yuuchan is getting tougher.
That's it...
Is it that bad?
Less than 5 minutes!
Five more minutes!
Hang in there!
Oh no, no, no!
But...
You've done it.
That's great
Good luck
Go for it
Go for it.
I'm glad you're here.
What's a pink big brother?
Hey, sis.
I changed my gender.
A lot.
My brain is buckwheat noodles.
Two more bowls and I'll be at 90.
I can make it 100.
I can go 100.
I can do it.
Yuuchan, I'm not writing in your handwriting.
Three more minutes.
It's written in dialect.
Delicious!
It's Ken-chan.
I'm starting to play with my toys.
Yuuchan is on the move
I'm off kilter
Tightly.
It's like a baseball game.
If music plays, I can eat
I'm sure it's good.
I like it.
That's good.
Hey, Mac.
Good luck.
Good work, sir.
Thank you for your hard work
Good work, sir.Thank you for your hard work
Two more bowls and we're at 100.
15 minutes elapsed
Yay!
3 more minutes to go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on
Everybody goes for a ride.
Come on, come on, come on, come on
Everybody's going for a ride
Oh, my God.
I'm impressed.
Hey.
They're coming.
Come on, guys, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'm going.
I'm coming.
Okay.
Good morning.
Come on.
Let's go, everyone!
Let's all go for a shot!
Look forward to it.
Looking forward to it.
One shot for everyone!
Thank you.
Twenty seconds!
Countdown!
They're counting down!
Ready!
Ten!
Eight!
Nine!
Four!
One!
Finished!
Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work!
So, I'm done eating Team Curculion!
Thank you for the food!
It was very delicious!
What do you think? Do you think you could be friends with soba?
We could be family!
As one!
It was delicious! I enjoyed the condiments too!
Well, I'll do it one at a time!
I had 84 cups!
Actually, I was aiming for 100 cups, so I'll do my best next time!
Yes, sir! I had 90 cups!
Thanks to my sister and everyone's support, I was able to do my best!
I had 107 cups!
That's amazing!
As a representative of soba lovers, I did my best!
My total number of one-course buses is now 490!
If I eat 100 more, I can drink enough!
Let's go for 1000!
Let's set our goal even higher and build a wall that no one can surpass!
Thank you for the food!
I hope to go to the next glass again!
So, I will be on the last team!
Thanks to everyone's hard work.
I just need to eat about 100 more glasses and I'll be clear while I ride.
We decided to set a record that no one can surpass at this point
Our anniversary of the decisive battle is August 9, so
I would like to aim for 809 cups!
I have an important announcement!
I am going to ask you to do it!
What! What!
It's been 10 years?
What's it gonna be? !What will it be!
The World's Most Innovative Wanko Soba Eating Grand Prix
Finalists 2023 are now the divine hankies!
In that case, I don't need to be cute.
I don't know what's so original about it.
But I'm going to do my best to achieve it anyway!
I'll do my best!
Please do!
We're a team of five.
Ready!
Yeah! Let's go!
Yes, sir! I'm hungry!
Tasty!
A little warm.
Yummy!
I don't know... vanilla milk or something next to it sounds good!
It's so good!
Really good!
It goes down your throat!
This one!
I'll take two!
Please!
Yummy!
That's a good phrase.
Sounds promising.
Yes, good luck!
Good luck!
Here you go!
Go for it!
He's walking too fast.
Over you go!
Your buddy's dragging his feet.
Go for it!
Delicious soba noodles!
Delicious, isn't it!
Delicious!
Here you go!
I can't stop laughing.
Oh, man.
It's so little.
Not many.
Here you go!
Here you go.
Okay, I'm off!
Bon appétit!
No, don't take a break.
Yes, sesame.
No, I'll do it once.
I'll do it once.
I'll do one.
You'll be fine.
Goma.
Sesame delicious?
Let's see some sesame seeds.
Yes, sir.
Yes, mampan.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Yes, here it comes!
Here it is!
Now, I'm going to eat it now.
It's delicious.
Yes, it's delicious!
Yes, 50 cups.
Thank you.
It's so good.
Is it back?
Yes, it's back.
Not really.
But it's pretty good.
Sweet.
Oh, go for it!
Go for it!
I want to do that one too.
Yes, go on, go on.
I want to do this one.
May I?
Wait, I'm scared.Wait, I'm scared.
Wait a minute, I'm scared.
Oh, shit.
Four more minutes.
Okay, go, go, go.
Oh, okay.
Five minutes.
Five minutes left.
Hang in there.
Five minutes?
Okay, go, go, go.
Keep going.
Okay, next.
Go, go, go, go.
Good luck.
Good luck!
youtubeDDAслN
-1
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
It is
k
- -.
out of date cup
-a -
that
root
Good luck!
But you guys are awesome!
That's great!
Make it an anniversary.
You don't have any more pieces!
Oh no!
Peace off!
Oh, my gosh!
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
Almost there!
You're doing great, Mon-chan
Hang in there, hang in there!
Yu-chan, your hair is a little...
No, no, no...
Yu has sweet hair
I'm serious
Serious mode
I don't know...
She's talking.
It's so big over here.
See?
Mon-chan's amazing.
If you notice that, it's better.
Yes, it is.
What? Tuna's delicious.
About a minute and 20 seconds left.
Next little bit.
Next few seconds.
Hang in there.
Oh, no, Magoo, you've given up!
About 30 seconds left.
Hang in there!
Don't lose!
I thought I lost.
Hold on a second.
Hang in there.
Ten.
Seven.
Ten. - Six. - Five.
Five.
Four.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you, I will be back soon.Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun.
God hanky done.
First, the number of losses.
It was 85.
It was 94.
I was 86th.
That's great.
No, maybe I can still do it.
Seriously?
Yeah.
That's cool.
That's what I'm talking about. The people of Iwate have a lot of heart.
They do it every morning.
Is that so?
Get up in the morning.
So that's all for now, the challenge of the Kamihanki team.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
All three teams have finished their questions!
Congratulations!
But I'm glad we got the one-cosmo we had longed for.
It's amazing, this sight.
This is the sight of the nine of us together.
I'm not lying.
Yes, it is.
And you know, we all received this special handprint.
Thank you very much.
Normally, you have to eat 100 bowls to receive a bill,
But this time, I was given a special delivery and record of everyone's meals for the photo shoot.
I was very moved.
Thank you very much.
It's so cute.
So cute.
Now, let's announce the results. First, one for each team.
And finally, the total.
OK.
Let's start with Papion.
Team Papion, total 214.
214.
This is important.
Team Curculion 281.
Oh.
Wow.
Amazing.
Team World's Most Innovative Wanko Soba Eating Grump Finalist 2023 Samiranki 2 65.
Oh.
Wow.
Everyone is over 200.
The total for the three teams is 760.
Wow.
That's amazing.
That's great.
We did it.
It's 3, isn't it?
It's 3, right?
We're way over our goal.
Like 100?
We're over 200.
That's great. I did my best.
I did my best.
It's wonderful.
This sight is amazing, isn't it?
Amazing.
This is 760.
Eh, wow.
I wonder how many hours it will take to do this live.
Karen wants to do it.
I'll be in detention after this.
I'm so proud of you.
We did what we set out to do.
Yes, we did.
It was great! It was delicious!
Anyway, the soba noodles are delicious!
I can eat so many buckwheat noodles!
It's not amazing that it's soba!
Amazing!
You should try it, too!We hope you will all
Come and try it the next morning!
By all means.
I hope you will all do the same.
Eat a lot of food and try to improve your record
Please try your best!
Please come and visit us in Iwate!
We're doing it, it's a great place!
Thank you very much for today's Bunder.
Thank you very much.
I would like to try something again!
Seino
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!